montagetalent.com 2012-05-12

# Website Privacy Policy

Welcome to Montage.  We are committed to protecting your privacy.  We have adopted this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to memorialize our data collection and disclosure practices for our website (the “Site”).  Montage voluntarily complies with the European Union – United States Safe Harbor Principles, and we invite you to review our Safe Harbor Privacy Statement below.

**Consent**

By using the Site, you consent to this Policy.  If you do not agree with this Policy, we ask that you refrain from use of the Site.  Information gathered through the Site may be transferred, used, and stored in the United States and in foreign jurisdictions in which we, our agents, customers, and other users of the Site are located.  If you access the Site, you consent to the transfer, use, and storage of your information in those jurisdictions.

**Collection of Information**

We collect personally identifiable information in connection with the Site.  The types of personal information collected may include your name, user name, address, email address, phone number, IP address, use and browser information as examples.  We may also collect non-personal and anonymous information to be used in an aggregate fashion.  For example, we may collect your system-related information to be used for system administration purposes, to help diagnose problems, to monitor traffic patterns, to determine which services are used most frequently and to assess site usage.  We may retain information we gather about you indefinitely unless otherwise required by applicable law. 

The Site may contain links to third party sites.  We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices, or content of sites owned by others that you may link to or that may be linked from the Site.  We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms and conditions of those sites so that you understand how those sites collect, use, and share your information.  This Policy applies solely to the information that we collect from our Site. 

**Cookies; Beacons**

From time to time, we may also use "cookies", “web beacons” or similar technology for the convenience of our users and to enhance your experience using the Site.  A cookie is a small text file that is recorded either temporarily or persistently on your hard drive by a web page server and is not used to deliver viruses or other harmful programs to your computer.  Rather, cookies enable us to recognize a user without requiring the user to repeatedly log in when using the Site.  Web beacons are graphics designed to collect web log information such as pages viewed or messages opened.  By relying on cookies, web beacons, and similar technology, we may be able to deliver a more efficient service that is more personalized for each user.   Additionally, these technologies may allow us to monitor traffic patterns, Site usage, and session information to make the Site more useful. 

**Use of Information**

We use information that we collect to assist us in improving and managing our operations.  Examples of such use include without limit:

  * Record keeping.
  * Sending promotional messages, special offers or other information that we think you may find helpful.
  * From time to time, contacting you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email, phone, fax or mail. We may use the information to customize the Site according to your interests.
  * Providing services to users of the Site in accordance with the general purposes of the Site.

**Disclosure of Information**

We may disclose personal information and aggregate anonymous information to companies, agents, contractors, or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf in connection with the Site.  We may also disclose personal information and aggregate anonymous information to those businesses, divisions, and units that are affiliated with Montage.  If one of our business lines or the entire business, or a substantial portion thereof, is acquired or transferred, whether by merger, consolidation or purchase of a substantial portion of assets, we may disclose and transfer your personally identifiable information to the acquiring third party.  We may also disclose your personal information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) enforce or apply the terms and conditions of the Site; (b) comply with legal or regulatory requirements; (c) protect the rights, property or safety of us, our users or other third parties; or (d) prevent a crime or protect national security.  We may also disclose aggregate anonymous information to our clients, business partners, merchants, advertisers, investors, potential buyers and other third parties if we deem such disclosure, in our discretion, to have sound business reasons or justification.

**Children**

We do not knowingly or specifically collect personal information from users under 13 years of age.  We do not authorize users under 13 years of age to use the Site.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to change this Policy at any time.  In particular, we may modify this Policy to reflect changes in the way we collect, use, or disclose information, or to reflect changes in privacy laws, regulations, and/or industry standards.  We encourage you to review this Policy when accessing the Site.  Continued use of the Site following changes indicates your acceptance of the changes. 

Applicable Law

This Policy shall be governed by the laws of the State of Wisconsin, USA, without regard to conflicts of law principles, and exclusive jurisdiction and venue for any dispute arising out of this Policy shall be the state courts or federal courts located in Wisconsin unless an alternate venue is provided for under the Safe Harbor Principles to which we have agreed with respect to matters covered by the Safe Harbor Principles.

EU-US Safe Harbor Privacy Statement

For personal information that Montage receives from the European Economic Area, we are committed to handling such personal information in accordance with the European Union Safe Harbor Principles.  For more information about the Safe Harbor Principles, please visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s website at [**http://export.gov/safeharbor**](http://export.gov/safeharbor).  As to all such personal information, these are our promises to you:

  * _Notice_.  When we collect your personal information, we’ll give you timely and appropriate notice describing what personal information we’re colleting, how we’ll use it, and the types of third parties with whom we may share it.

  * _Choice_.  We’ll give you choices about the ways we use and share your personal information, and we’ll respect the choices you make.

  * _Relevance_.  We’ll collect only as much personal information as we need for specific, identified purposes, and we won’t use it for other purposes without obtaining your consent.

  * _Retention_.  We’ll keep your personal information only as long as we need it for the purposes for which we collected it, or as permitted by law.

  * _Accuracy_.  We’ll take appropriate steps to make sure the personal information in our records is accurate.

  * _Access_.  We’ll provide ways for you to access your personal information, as required by law, so you can correct inaccuracies or provide ways for you to contact us so that we can correct any inaccuracies.

  * _Security_.  We’ll take appropriate physical, technical, and organizational measures to protect personal information from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction.

  * _Sharing_.  Except as described in this Policy, we won’t share your personal information with third parties without your consent.

  * _International Transfer_.  If we transfer your personal information to another country, we’ll take appropriate measures to protect your privacy and the personal information we transfer.

  * _Enforcement_.  We’ll regularly review how we’re meeting these privacy promises, and we’ll provide an independent way to resolve complaints about our privacy practices.

U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor

Montage complies with the U.S. –EU safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland.  Montage has certified that it adheres to the Safe harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.  To learn more about the Safe harbor program, and to view Montage’s certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/

Contact Information  
To access your information, ask questions about our privacy practices, or to submit a complaint, please contact us at:   
Montage Talent, Inc.  
514 Wells Street, Suite C  
Delafield, WI 53018  
Phone:  262.264.5964  
Fax: 262.303.4189  
Email: [privacy@montagetalent.com.com](mailto:privacy@montagetalent.com.com)

Effective Date:  September 14, 2011
